misterbandb.com 2019-05-24

# Privacy Policy - misterb&b Help Center

Last Updated: March 30, 2018

Thank you for reviewing misterb&b, Inc.'s (if you reside in any country outside of the European Union) or Pinklab360 SASU/misterb&b Europe (if you reside in the European Union) (collectively referred to as "misterb&b", “we,” “us” or “our”) privacy policy for its mobile application (“App”) and Internet web sites located at the URL’s www.misterbandb.com ("Site"). This Privacy Policy details certain policies implemented throughout misterb&b governing misterb&b's collection and use of personally identifiable information about users of our Site and users of our App.

Information Collection and Use.

You can generally visit our Site and use our App without having to submit any personally identifiable information about yourself to us. However, to use certain services and functionality of the Site and the App (such as to post a property for rent or request to book a rental property), you will be required to register for an account with misterb&b. When you register for an account, we will collect your name, email address, mailing address, gender, sexual orientation, username and password. If you are a posting a property for rent, we will also collect the address of the rental property and we may request your photo, identification or passport copy and/or copies of your utility bills. If you signup to receive our newsletters, we will collect your email address to send you our newsletters.

If you contact us with questions or to request information, we will collect the personally identifiable information that you voluntarily transmit with your communications to us. We also may collect personally identifiable information about you that you elect to upload to the Site or our App (such as in rental property descriptions or ratings for properties).

We may use your personally identifiable information to register you to use our Site and App and to provide our rental platform services to you, contact you to deliver certain services or information you have requested, verify your authority to use the App and the Site, to detect fraud, improve the content and general administration of the Site and the App. We may use your photo, identification or passport copy and/or copies of your utility bills to verify your identity. We may also send you targeted marketing and promotions regarding our App and the Site. If you do not wish to receive these marketing or promotions from us, you may opt-out as set forth in the message.

If you register to use our Site, you may engage in direct messages with another user through the Site or App. misterb&b may collect personally identifiable information that you include in such messages and may review such messages from time-to-time for purposes of confirming compliance with misterb&b’s Terms of Use or to detect and/or investigate email scams or similar fraudulent activities.

You may import the contacts from your address book to your misterb&b account. You can also send an e-mail to contacts you manually select, inviting them to join misterb&b. If you wish to activate this feature, we may access your Gmail address book contacts by using the OAuth 2.0 protocol. We will not store or share information about contacts; we will however store the email addresses you sent invitations to. 

Additionally, the third party app store providers from which you obtain the App may collect certain data about you, including aggregate data, and your use of the applicable app store is subject to the privacy policy terms of the app store provider. The app store providers may provide us with certain aggregate data about you.

Children’s Privacy.

misterb&b recognizes the privacy interests of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests. Neither the Site nor the App are directed to children under the age of 13. misterb&b does not target its App or this Site to children under 13. misterb&b does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that a child under the age of 13 provided us with personally identifiable information, we will delete that information. If your child has provided personally identifiable information, please contact us so we can delete it. If you are under the age of 13, please do not provide us with any personally identifiable information.

Cookies.

We may use small text files called cookies to improve overall Site experience. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Cookies generally do not permit us to personally identify you.  We generally use session cookies to save your preferences and such cookies expire when you close your browser. We also may set a persistent cookie to authenticate users (such as for password recognition) and for support for the internal operations of our Site and App. misterb&b may track users over time and over our Sites but we do not respond to browser do not track signals.

Third parties such as providers of external services like web traffic analysis services may also track users over time and over our Site and third party websites and such third parties may also place cookies, via our Site. These cookies are likely to be analytical, performance cookies or targeting cookies, including:

Google Analytics cookies, which in particular are used as misterb&b contracts with Google as a third party vendor. You can find out more about this popular website analytics tool here: http://www.google.com/analytics/index.html. These cookies collect information about how visitors use a website, for instance which pages visitors go to most often, and if they get error messages from web pages. These cookies don’t collect information that identifies a visitor. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. It is only used to improve how a website works. All of this information is anonymized. You can find out more about how it protects your data here: <http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html>

Social Plugins on Our Site and App.

We may use social plugins on our Site and App and may include icons that allow you to interact with third party social networks such as Twitter and Facebook. For example, you may sign in to the Site with Facebook and you may “like” us on Facebook or follow us on Twitter. The third party social plugin may set a cookie when your browser creates a connection to the servers of such social networks and the plugin may transmit your data to the social networks. Your use of these social plugins is subject to the privacy policies of the third party social networks.

Aggregate Information.

Through the third party analytic providers, as discussed above, and directly through our Site, we may track information that will be maintained, used and disclosed in aggregate form only and which will not contain your personally identifiable information. For example, without limitation, the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, browser type, External Web Sites (defined below) linked to and IP addresses. We may analyze this data for trends and statistics in the aggregate, and we may use such aggregate information to administer the Site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

Disclosure.

Any information, including personally identifiable information that you include in a rental property listing (such as address or photos) will be publicly available on the Site and App. If you are a guest that books a rental through the Site and/or the App we will transmit your name, contact information and username to the rental property host to enable you to enter into a rental agreement with such host. If you are a host that offers your rental property on the Site and/or App, we will transmit your name, contact information and username to the guests that book your rental property.

We may provide your personally identifiable information and the data generated by cookies and the aggregate information to the vendors and service agencies that we may engage to assist us in providing our services to you for their use solely to provide us with such assistance. For example, we use third party payment processors to process your payments, our Site is hosted by a third party hosting provider and we use a third party to conduct fraud detection services on our Site and/or App. Such third parties’ use of your personally identifiable information is subject to the third party’s applicable privacy policy terms and we may also enter into Model Contracts for the transfer of personal data to third countries with such third party vendors and service agencies. If we remit taxes, such as occupancy taxes, on your behalf as a lessor, we will provide your name and contact information to the local tax authorities.

We will also disclose your personally identifiable information (a) if we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority or otherwise in cooperation with an ongoing investigation of a governmental authority, (b) to enforce the misterb&b Terms of Use or user agreements or to protect our rights or (c) to protect the safety of users of our Site and our services. We will not sell your personally identifiable information to any company or organization, but we may transfer your personally identifiable information to a successor entity upon a merger, consolidation or other corporate reorganization in which misterb&b participates or to a purchaser or acquirer of all or substantially all of misterb&b's assets to which this Site and/or the App relates.

Links to Third Party Sites.

The Site may provide links to other web sites or resources over which misterb&b does not have control ("External Web Sites"). Such links do not constitute an endorsement by misterb&b of those External Web Sites. You acknowledge that misterb&b is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and further agree that misterb&b is not responsible for the content of such External Web Sites. Your use of External Web Sites is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies located on the linked to External Web Sites.

Security.

We may employ procedural and technological measures that are generally consistent with industry practice. Such measures are reasonably designed to help protect your personally identifiable information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. misterb&b may use encryption, secure socket layer and password protection to help prevent unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information.

Updating Personally Identifiable Information.

misterb&b provides you with the ability to review, update and delete the registration information that you provide to us by accessing and modifying this information in your account online or by contacting us at support (@) misterbandb.com.

Questions.

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy please contact us via email at support (@) misterbandb.com.

Users Outside of the United States.

Our computer systems and third party hosting provider systems are currently based in the United States, so your personal data will be processed by us in the U.S. where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as the European Union. If you create a user account with the App or the Site as a visitor from outside the United States, by using the App or the Site you agree to this Privacy Policy and you consent to the transfer of all such information to the United States, which may not offer an equivalent level of protection of that required in the European Union or certain other countries, and to the processing of that information as described in this Privacy Policy. Please note that we also may enter into Model Contracts for the transfer of personal data from Pinklab360 SASU/misterb&b Europe to SFO84, Inc./misterb&b and with our third party vendors and service agencies.

#### Modification

misterb&b reserves the right, at its sole discretion to modify the Terms of the Privacy Policy, at any time.

If we modify these Terms, we will post the change on the Site (as defined below) or via the App. We will also update the “Last Updated Date” at the top of these Terms. We will provide you with notice of the modifications by email at least thirty (30) days before the date they become effective. If you disagree with the revised Privacy Policy, you may cancel your misterb&b account. If you do not cancel you misterb&b account before the date it becomes effective, you are indicating that you accept the modified Privacy Policy.
